<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RMC Robo Club</title>
    <link>http://robo.segfaults.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RMC Robo Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 23:49:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://robo.segfaults.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printing</title>
      <link>http://robo.segfaults.net/workshops/3d-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 23:49:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://robo.segfaults.net/workshops/3d-printing/</guid>
      <description>Goal To design and build/print a thingamajig for the Robo Club
What? The workshop will be based around engineering design of a part (to be determined).
Part one of the workshop will be a discussion/brainstorm session of what we are trying to build, determining specs/requirements and considerations for the design. Part two of the workshop will be a quick introduction to the 3D-printing toolchain and discussion of the use of 3D printing in engineering designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://robo.segfaults.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 23:49:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://robo.segfaults.net/about/</guid>
      <description>RoboClub The RMC Robotics Club is a club that does robotics at RMC.
We meet every Monday and Tuesday at 19h00, sometimes to work on robots, sometimes to attend workshops to improve our general &amp;lsquo;making&amp;rsquo; skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://robo.segfaults.net/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 23:37:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://robo.segfaults.net/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>If you are interested in participating please email s27714 at rmc dot ca</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Meeting</title>
      <link>http://robo.segfaults.net/posts/first-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 23:49:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://robo.segfaults.net/posts/first-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Starting Out Quick presentation about where we might be able to take the club.
Discussion What did those present want to do with the club?
Not a kit It was obvious that folks were more interested in following through the complete design process than simply putting together their own small robot.
Although initially we will not have the resourses or comitment to tackle something as huge as a self driving car or small spacecraft, we plan to create a couple of smaller robots in teams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>